You can't keep a good cop dead.
Dead Heat is a action, horror, science fiction film directed by Mark Goldblatt.
Detective Roger Mortis is killed in action while investigating a string of mysterious robberies: until
he's brought back from the dead with a chemical company's secret re-animation technology.
Now he has twelve hours to solve the case of his own
death before he dies: And stays dead.
Det. Roger Mortis, played by Treat Williams.
Det. Doug Bigelow, played by Joe Piscopo.
Randi James, played by Lindsay Frost.
Dr. Ernest McNab, played by Darren McGavin.
Arthur P. Loudermilk, played by Vincent Price.
Lt. Herzog, played by Robert Picardo.
Dead Heat is a 1988 American buddy cop action zombie comedy film directed by Mark Goldblatt and
starring Treat Williams, Joe Piscopo, Darren McGavin, Lindsay Frost and Vincent Price.
The film is about an LAPD police officer who is murdered while attempting to arrest zombies who have been reanimated by the head of Dante
Laboratories in order to carry out violent armed robberies, and decides to get revenge with the help of his former partner.
The film explores themes of police, undead, resurrection, zombie, zombification.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.